오리랑 병아리 사이에
새끼 태어나면 좋겠지?
Wouldn't it be cool if our duck
and our chick had a baby?
We could call it Chuck.
'리리'라고 부를 테야
'오아리'는 어때?
Or Dick.
- 얘들아
- 왔냐?
Listen, I need a favor.
부탁 하나 할게
I was in the shower,
and as I was...
샤워하다가...
...cleansing myself, I felt something.
씻고 있는데
뭔가 이상한 거야
Was it like a sneeze, only better?
재채기 나고 그래?
아니, 몸에 뭐가 났다니까
No. I mean, like,
a thing on my body.
Well, what was it?
뭔데?
몰라, 그게 위치가...
Well, I don't know.
It's kind of in a place that's not....
It's not visually accessible to me.
And I was hoping maybe you guys...
내 시야 밖이거든
그래서 너희가 좀
봐줬으면 해
...could help me out.
싫어!
좀 해줘
별 거 아냐
Come on, you guys!
It's no big deal!
Well, what is it?
Is it a mole?
뭔데? 사마귀야?
사마귀라기엔
주름이 많아
No, it's too wrinkly to be a mole.
그럼 뾰루지야?
Is it?
What, a pimple?
뾰루지라기엔
너무 화려한데
No, it's...
...fancier than a pimple.
-Ross, just go see a doc
-Guys, what's?
- 그냥 병원에...
- 저기...
그래, 확실해
2주만 있어봐
Well, it's definite.
Two more weeks of winter.
맞아
Yeah, right.
The One With Ross' Thing
And this is the coffeehouse.
This is where I play my music.
여기가 커피 하우스고
저기서 노래하죠
-Good deal.
-These are my friends.
좋군요
제 친구들이에요
People? This is Vince.
Vince, the people.
얘들아, 빈스야
빈스, 애들이에요
반가워요
Vince is a fireman.
빈스는 소방관이야
불타는 건물에서
사람도 구해보셨어요?
Have you ever rescued anyone
from a burning building?
Ninety-eight hot saves.
Highest on the force.
98명으로 1등입니다
If Joey and I play with matches,
we could get you up to an even 100.
조이랑 제가 불장난해서
100명 채워드리죠
Fire safety is not a joke, son.
불조심은 장난이 아니지
물론 아니죠
You're right. I know.
가볼게요, 밤에 전화하죠
토요일에 봐요
Look, I gotta go.
I'm on call tonight.
See you Saturday.
그래요
멋있다, 근데 너
유치원 교사 만났잖아?
He's cute, Pheebs.
But you just started dating
that teacher.
- 제이슨?
- 그래
Oh, Jason?
오늘밤에 만나
We're seeing each other tonight.
하루에 두 사람을 만나?
너답지 않아
Well, Pheebs?
Two dates in one day?
That's so unlike you.
나도 알아
그냥 양다리야
I know, I know.
I'm, like, playing the field.
젊음을 맘껏
불태우는 거야
I'm juggling two guys.
I'm sowing my wild oats.
불타는 양다리라고
할 수 있지
You know, this kind of, like,
oat-sowing, field-playing juggler.
그거 남자들도 알아?
So do they know about each other?
Does a dog's lips move
when he reads?
개가 책 볼 때
입술 움직이디?
Okay, no, they don't know.
그래, 안 움직여
Hey, guys.
- 나 왔어
- 안녕
- 어땠어?
- 병원에서 뭐래?
-Well?
-How'd it go at the doctor's?
He said there's definitely
nothing to worry about. It's benign.
양성종양이니까
전혀 걱정할 것 없대
-What is it?
-He couldn't even tell me.
- 정체가 뭐래?
- 아무 말 못하더라구
일종의 피부병이란
말만 했어
He said it was just
some sort of "skin abnormality."
The worse thing is, he said,
being unable to identify it...
게다가 확인되기 전까진
제거도 못해주겠대잖아
... he was reluctant to remove it.
내 주치의한테 가봐
내 세 번째 젖꼭지를
You should go to my guy.
Because when I went in there
with my third nipple...
...he just lopped it right off.
- 시원하게 떼주더라구
- 그래?
운이 좋았지
So I guess I'm lucky.
I mean, not as lucky as people
who are born with two nipples.
젖꼭지 두 개로 태어난
사람엔 쨉이 안 되지만
네 건 뭔지도 알고
병명이라도 있었지
At least they knew what yours was.
You know? Yours had a name.
네 이름을 따면 되겠네
Maybe they'll name yours after you.
'로스'라고 말야
You know?
They'd call it "The Ross."
And then people would be, like,
"Oh, he's got a Ross."
사람들은 이러겠지
'걔 로스가 났어'
Yeah, that'd be cool.
좋은 생각이다
Pete's breaking up with me.
- 피트가 헤어지자고 할 건가봐
- 뭐?
What?
I just checked my messages.
메시지를 확인해봤더니
애틀랜타 다녀와서
He said that when he gets back,
"We need to talk."
'긴히 할 말'이 있대
-And?
-Well, that's it.
근데?
그거야, 긴히 할 말이란 건
십중팔구 나쁜 얘기라구
People never say, "We need to talk,"
unless it's something bad.
헤어지잔 소리라고
단정할 순 없지
That doesn't necessarily mean
he's breaking up with you.
Really?
정말?
바람정도 피는 거겠지
Maybe he just cheated on you.
돈은 많이 못 벌지만
I won't get rich doing it,
but I gotta say, it's cool...
아이들이 변해 가는
모습을 보면 정말 기뻐요
... knowing you're making
a difference in a kid's life.
That is so great.
정말 멋있어요
맙소사!
Oh, my God!
- 소방서에 신고해야겠어요
- 안돼요!
We'd better call
the fire department.
안 된다구요?
Well, we don't need a fireman.
소방관보단 솜씨 좋은
정비공이나 부르죠
We need, like, a good mechanic.
어떡해? 오고 있잖아
얼른 도망쳐요
Here they come!
We gotta get out of here!
잠깐만요, 왜요?
Wait. Why?
소방관 만나면 콱
사귀어버릴 거예요
If I wanted to see a fireman,
I'd date one.
세 번째 젖꼭지 아시죠?
식은 죽 먹기잖아요?
That's all it is.
A third nipple.
You know? Just your
run-of-the-mill third nipple.
그거라고 생각하시고
당장 떼어주세요
You can take it off.
Just slice that baby right off.
Take your shirt off.
Let's see what we're dealing with.
셔츠 벗어요
뭔지 좀 봅시다
What are you doing?
뭐 하는 거죠?
Just showing you my run-of-the-mill,
slice-it-right-off third nipple.
식은 죽 먹기
세 번째 젖꼭지 보시라구요
세 번째 젖꼭지랑은 다르군요
Well, that's not a third nipple.
First of all, it's on your ass.
일단 궁둥이에 있잖아요?
Well, then what is it?
그럼 이게 뭐죠?
Wait a minute. Hold it.
잠시 기다리세요
- 젠슨, 잠깐 들어오게
- 해밀튼도 같이 있어요
-Jansen, come in here.
-I'm with Hamilton!
He's good with weird things.
Bring him in too.
희귀병 전문이니
마침 잘 됐군
피트 화초에 물줘야지
I gotta go water Pete's plants.
You know what? If he's gonna break up
with me, maybe I won't water them.
헤어질 거라면
내가 왜 물을 줘?
그렇다면 조이랑 내가
물을 줘야겠군
If he's gonna break up with you,
maybe Joey and I should do it...
...if you know what I mean.
뭔 뜻인지 알지?
Or...
아니면 거기 가서
쉬나 해주든가
...we could go and pee on them.
I can't take it, you know.
못해먹겠어
들킬까봐 겁나죽겠다니까
정말 미쳐버리겠어
I'm afraid one of them
will catch me with the other.
It's making me crazy!
그럼 한 명은
포기해야겠네
Why don't you break up
with one of them?
양다리 전선에
문제 생겼어?
What happened to playing the field?
좋을 줄만 알았는데
It doesn't feel like playing anymore.
다리몽둥이 부러지게 생겼어
It's feels like work.
It's like I'm working in the field.
So pick one of them.
- 하나만 택해
- 누가 더 좋은데?
Which one do you like more?
Vince is great, you know?
Because he's, like, a "guy" guy.
빈스는 남자 중의 남자라서
맘에 들어, 엄청 우람하잖아
He's just so burly,
so very burly.
무지 우람해
Okay, good. So there you go.
Go with Vince.
딱이네, 빈스로 해
제이슨은 감성적이야
But Jason's really sensitive.
감성이 중요하지
그 사람 해
Sensitive is important.
Pick him.
그래
Oh, sure.
Go with the sissy.
계집애 같으니...
Jason is not a sissy.
제이슨은 계집애 아냐
오해 마
챈들러 얘기야
I meant Chandler.
You know, I have dinner plans.
저 저녁 약속 있다구요
Thank you so much for coming
on such a short notice.
급하게 모셨는데도
와주셨군요
의사 경력이 23년이나 된
저로서도
Ladies and gentlemen, I've been
practicing medicine for 23 years...
...and I'm stumped.
난감하답니다
여기가 서재야
잠깐 있어봐
Okay, this is the den.
All right, check this out.
Lights!
불!
약한 불!
어두운 불!
All right, less lights!
Bad lights!
Lights, go away!
꺼져라 불!
See? You just need the right command.
명령만 제대로 하면 돼
스위치로 조절하든가
And the dimmer switch.
For a rich guy, that's a small TV.
부자 TV가 이렇게 작아?
그건 비디오폰이야
That's the video phone.
But you shouldn't be here.
So don't touch anything.
몰래 데려온 거니까
함부로 만지지 마
IKEA, this is comfortable!
캬! 이 편안함!
This place is amazing!
집 정말 끝내준다
-Oh, God! That's the nicest kitchen.
-I know.
- 저런 주방 처음 봤어
- 그래
It's the nicest kitchen.
냉장고가 말을 하더라니까
'좋은 하루 되세요! '
The refrigerator
told me to have a great day.
Look, a millionaire's checkbook.
백만장자의 수표책이네
Joey, put that down.
조이, 내려놔
Oh, my God, that's Pete.
Get out!
피트 전화야
다들 숨어
How the hell do you answer
a video phone?
비디오폰은 어떻게 받지?
모니카?
I guess that's how.
이렇게 받는 거군
모니카, 잘 지내요?
Monica, how's it going?
그럼요, 좋아요
물 주러 온 거예요
Oh, it's good. It's good.
Just here, watering the plants.
레이첼 옆 고무나무도
잊지 마요
Don't forget that ficus
there by Rachel.
Chandler's on the couch!
챈들러는 소파에 있대요
I see him. You guys
are the worst hiders, ever.
다 보여요
꼭꼭 숨었어야죠
-Hi.
-How you doing?
- 안녕하세요?
- 반가워요
피트, 긴히 할 말 있댔죠?
기쁜 소식인가요, 아닌가요?
The other day when you said
you needed to talk...
...just so I know,
is it good news or bad news?
It's good news.
It's definitely good news.
기쁜 소식이에요
아주 기쁜 소식이죠
잠깐만요
딴 전화가 왔어요
Hold on a second,
I have another call.
안녕하세요?
How's it going?
아직 저예요
It's still me.
아뇨, 딴 사람한테
말한 거예요
I've got picture-in-picture here.
I'm gonna have to call you back later.
그래요, 나중에 다시
전화할게요
Monica? You.
I'm gonna have to call you back.
모니카!
다시 전화한다구요
알았어요
나중에 봐요
So I'll see you soon.
-Okay. I love you.
-I love you.
- 사랑해요
- 저도 사랑해요
저희도 사랑해요
We love you too!
기쁜 소식이래
기쁜 소식!
Well, it's good news.
It's good news.
- 어떤 기쁜 소식일까?
- 이것 봐!
-What do you think the good news is?
-Look at this!
'휴고 린드그렌 링 디자인'에
5만 달러나 썼네
He wrote a check for $50,000
to "Hugo Lindgren's Ring Design."
Sorry. What do you think
the good news is?
미안!
기쁜 소식이 뭘까?
Oh, my!
세상에!
모니카가 백만장자랑 결혼해!
Monica's gonna marry a millionaire!
엄마한테 전화해
엄마한테! 엄마한테!
You gotta get Mom on the phone!
Call Mom! Call Mom!
여보세요?
And that's Pete's mom.
피트 엄마야
You have to make it a theme wedding.
And the theme could be:
결혼식을 특별하게 해
제목은...
'우리 정말 돈 많죠?'
"Look How Much Money We've Got!"
초대장에도 돈을 넣고
접시도 돈으로 만들어
I mean, you could put money
in the invitations.
You could have, like,
little-money place settings.
돈 샐러드는 어때?
And you could start
with a money salad.
맛은 없어도
사람들은 좋아할 거야
I mean, it'll be dry,
but people will like it.
그만해, 만난 지 얼마 되지도
않았고 아직 확실치도 않잖아
Would you stop?
We've only gone out a couple of weeks.
We don't know if he'll propose.
피트는 보통 사람하곤 달라
첫 데이트 때 로마 데려갔지?
But this is Pete.
He's not like other people.
On your first date, you went to Rome.
For most guys, that's like
a third or fourth date kind of thing.
보통 사람은 서너 번째쯤에나
가능한 거라구
Well, if that's what it is,
then it's crazy.
만약 그렇대도
당치도 않아
Monica's right.
We're talking about marriage here.
맞아, 이건 결혼 문제야
신중하게 생각해야 돼
She can't just rush into this.
레즈비언하고 결혼한
주제에 나서긴?
What do you know?
You married a lesbian!
빈스한테 헤어지자고
말하러 간다
I gotta go.
I have to break up with Vince.
교사랑 사귀는 거야?
So you're going with the teacher?
빈스도 정말 좋지만
제이슨은 감성적이니까
I like Vince a lot, you know?
But Jason is so sensitive.
길게 보면 감성적인 게
더 낫지
In the long run, I think
sensitive is better than having...
빈스의 섹시하고 섹시하고
섹시한... 몸보다는
...a really, really, really nice body.
Jason. Definitely Jason.
제이슨이고 말고!
- 행운을 빌어줘
- 잘해
-Wish me luck!
-Good luck!
Oh, my God!
Sorry.
미안, 돈다발 부케를
받는 상상을 했거든
I was imagining what it'd be like
to catch the money bouquet.
실례지만, 빈스 있나요?
Excuse me. Is Vince here?
네
빈스!
Oh, sure.
그걸 진짜 타긴 타네요
I didn't know you guys
actually used those.
So what's up?
웬일이에요?
말하기 좀 곤란한데...
This isn't gonna be easy.
I don't think we should
see each other anymore.
이제 그만 헤어지자구요
Good deal.
이럴 수가!
I'm sorry.
미안해요
괜찮아요
No, it's okay.
It's just that I thought
we had something pretty special here.
우리 관계는
특별하다고 생각했죠
I felt like you were someone
I could finally open up to.
당신 앞에선
솔직해질 수 있었고
There's so much in me
I haven't shared with you yet.
함께 하고 싶은 게
너무 많은데...
My God!
I didn't know you were so
- 세상에! 당신 정말...
- 말로 표현 못 해요
I'm sorry. I can't talk.
I'm gonna go write in my journal.
일기장에 쓰러 갈래요
잠깐만요!
Wait! Wait! Wait!
If you wanna take care of that thing,
go see my herbal guy.
생각 있으면 내가 아는
향치료사한테 가보라구
Thanks. But I wanna remove it,
not make it savory.
뾰루지 없애고 싶댔지
향기 나게 하겠대?
When girls sleep with guys
with weird things on their body...
여자들은 같이 잔 남자 몸에
이상한 거 있으면 소문낸다
...they tell their friends about it.
줘봐
Give me that.
화내지 마
어쩔 수가 없었어
Okay, don't be mad at me,
but I couldn't resist.
Bride's Magazines?
신부 잡지네
안타깝게도 넌 청혼을
거절하겠다고 했지만
I know you said you'd say no
if he asked you...
... but how great would you look
walking down the aisle...
이걸 입고 입장하면
얼마나 멋질까?
도나 카렌이야
...in this Donna Karan?
정말 예쁘다!
You so would!
You should get that anyway.
일단 사놓고 봐
Well, for clubbing.
예쁘잖아
It is so weird.
참 이상해
어제 그렇게 말해놓곤
I know what I said.
But this morning...
오늘 아침에 침대에 누워
승낙하면 어떨까 생각해봤어
...I was lying in bed, imagining
what it'd be like to say yes.
I know it's a little sudden,
and it's rushed...
너무 갑작스러운 일이고
나답지 않은 행동이지만
...and it's not like me to do
something like this.
But it doesn't mean I can't.
Right?
못 할 것도 없잖아
I mean, I'm crazy about Pete.
피트가 너무 좋고
우린 바라는 것도 같지
And I know that
we want the same things.
And when I thought
about saying yes...
승낙하는 생각을 하니까
너무 행복했어
...it made me really happy.
Oh, my God!
어머나!
I know.
그래!
파이 더 먹을래
I need more pie.
Mon, if you do get married,
can I bring two guests?
식장에 파트너 두 명
데려가도 돼?
You didn't break up with that fireman?
소방수랑 안 끝냈어?
내 말이 그 말이야
That was my way of telling you.
Well, it turns out
he's incredibly sensitive.
진짜 감성적인 사람이더라구
일기도 쓰고 그림도 그려
He keeps a journal and he paints.
날 그린 목탄화도 보여줬어
He even showed me charcoal drawings
that he drew of me.
He'd prefer watercolors, but he has
easy access to a lot of charcoal.
수채화를 더 좋아한다는데
숯 구하기가 더 쉽잖아
So will you dump Jason?
제이슨이랑 끝내야겠네?
Yeah, because I have to break up
with someone.
응, 하나는 정리해야 되니까
So Jason is sensitive.
But now, so is Vince.
제이슨은 감성적이야
근데 빈스도 그래
빈스는 몸까지 죽이는데
Plus, Vince has the body.
You know?
So....
It's really just about the math.
계산 끝난 거지 뭐
- 제이슨?
- 들어와요
Come on in.
You sounded serious on the phone.
전화 목소리가 안 좋던데
무슨 일 있어요?
Is anything wrong?
일은요?
로스로군요?
You must be Ross.
안녕하세요?
사즈 도사입니다
I am Guru Saj.
Listen, I gotta tell you, I've never
been to a guru before, so....
도사한텐 처음 와봐서
말인데요...
걱정 말아요
Well, relax.
If it makes you feel any better,
I've attended...
중미에서 가장 좋은 의대를
다녔다면 안심하시겠어요?
...fine medical schools
in Central America.
Well, let's take a look
at this skin abnormality of yours.
어떤 피부병인지 볼까요?
Come on, have a seat.
앉으세요
As I suspected, it's a kundus.
짐작대로군요
'쿤더스'예요
What's a "kundus"?
쿤더스가 뭐죠?
I don't know.
What's a kundus with you?
댁의 쿤더스는
대체 뭘까요?
Please lie down.
자, 엎드리세요
연고만 바르면 싹 가라앉죠
I've got a salve that
ought to shrink that right up.
I guess it's worth a try.
- 효과가 있어야 될 텐데
- 그럼요, 결과 보시면...
Sure. We should see results
이게 아니군 그래!
Clearly not the way to go!
What? What?
뭐예요?
We appear to have angered it.
- 우리가 화를 불렀어요
- 우리요? 화라뇨?
We? We angered it?
I think I see the problem.
이제야 알겠군요
And I'm afraid we're gonna
have to use a much stronger tool.
훨씬 강력한 방법을
쓰는 수 밖에요
Love.
사랑이죠
Oh, God!
맙소사!
로스, 치료할 수 있는
방법은 하나뿐이에요
There is absolutely no way
this is gonna come off...
이제부터...
... unless you start to....
What was that?
뭐예요?
Well, it's gone.
없어졌어요
어떻게요?
How's that?
Got caught in my watch.
시계에 걸렸어요
조명!
Lights.
로맨틱 조명!
Romantic lights.
좋네요
Nice.
So there was this thing
I wanted to talk to you about.
할 얘기 있다고 했었죠?
맞다! 까맣게
잊고 있었어요
Oh, right. I'd completely
forgot about that.
I've been doing a lot of thinking.
고민 많이 했어요
And I look at my life...
제 삶을 돌아보면...
사업은 이미 크게 성공했고
...and I feel like I've conquered
the business world.
And I feel like I've conquered
the intellectual world.
지적으로도 우수하다고
할 수 있죠
And now I have the most
beautiful woman in the world.
아름다운 여인도
곁에 있구요
한 가지가 빠졌어요
But there's one thing missing.
What's that?
뭐죠?
It's time for me to conquer
the physical world.
강인한 육체에 도전할
때가 온 거죠
그래서요?
얼티밋 파이팅 챔피언이
되고 싶어요
I wanna become...
...the Ultimate Fighting Champion.
You wanna what?
뭐 어째요?
UFC, 격투기 말예요
I wanna be
the Ultimate Fighting Champion.
It's the most intense
physical competition in the world.
너무 격렬하다보니
49개 주에서 금지됐죠
It's banned in 49 states.
What are you talking about?
무슨 얘기예요?
'지쿤도'와 브라질 격투기를
접목해서 배우고 있어요
My trainer, Hoshi, is teaching me...
...Jeet Kune Do
and Brazilian streetfighting.
훈련용 8각 링도 주문했죠
I even had my own
octagon training ring designed.
And I suppose you used
a ring designer for that.
링 디자이너를
그래서 썼군요
그래요
모니카, 승리의 순간에
맨 앞줄에 앉아줘요
I want you there,
in the front row, when I win.
I want you close enough
to smell the blood.
승리를 만끽하라구요
어때요?
What do you think?
우리 부모님이
좋아하실 거예요
My parents will be so happy.
미친 속옷은
엉덩이를 기어올라
Crazy underwear
Creeping up my butt
Always in a rut
미친 속옷은
맨날 밝히기만 해
Crazy underwear
미친 속옷...
여긴 웬일이지?
What is he doing here?
All right, just keep playing.
그냥 노래나 하자
잘 해낼 거야
괜찮아
You'll get through this.
You'll be fine.
@#$ % &#?@#
Okay, thank you.
고맙습니다
And as always, no one talk to me
after the show.
아무도 저한테
말 걸지 마세요
안녕
I was passing by
and saw you were playing.
지나다가 당신이 노래한다기에
들어왔는데 멋지네요
This is cool, seeing you up there.
이봐요!
What's going on here?
Who's this guy?
뭐 하는 거예요?
누구죠?
몰라요, 막 키스했어요
잡아요, 빈스!
I don't know! He just started
kissing me. Get him, Vince!
What?
- 네?
- 뭐요?
사실은 양다리 걸쳤어요
I've been dating both of you.
And it's been really horrible,
because it's been...
정말 끔찍했죠
왜냐하면...
...a lot of fun for me.
저야 좋았지만요
But I like you both...
둘 다 좋아서
선택할 수가 없었죠
...and I didn't know how to choose.
미안해요, 잘못했어요
제가 정말 나빴어요
So I'm sorry. I'm terrible.
I'm a terrible person.
피비, 괜찮아요
한 사람만 만나란 법 있나요?
Relax. It's okay.
I mean....
We never said this was exclusive.
그래요, 죄책감 버려요
Neither did we.
So give yourself a break.
Really?
정말요?
사귄 지도 얼마 안 됐고
잠도 같이 안 잤잖아요?
We haven't been going out that long.
Come on, we haven't even
slept together yet.
You haven't?
안 잤어요?
You have?
잤어요?
Well, this is none of my business.
전 빠질게요
I can't believe this!
You slept with him?
어쩜 그럴 수가!
저 사람이랑 잤어요?
Well, I made you
a candlelight dinner in the park.
공원에서 촛불만찬
해줬잖아요
피비, 난 알아서 빠져드리죠
I'm gonna make this real easy for you.
정말 어색해질 뻔했네요
That could've been really awkward.
You made him a candlelight dinner
in the park?
공원에서 촛불만찬을
했다구요?
Yeah, but I can do that for you.
I'm gonna do that for you.
당신한테도 해줄게요
숲에서 불장난이나 하는 사람과
데이트했다니 믿을 수가 없어!
I can't believe
I went out with somebody...
...who'd have an open flame
in the middle of a wooded area!
Everything's gonna be all right.
조금만 참아
Okay, Dick?
알았지, 오아리?
Hello. I am Guru Saj.
전 사즈 도사입니다
He's a duck, right?
Because otherwise...
오리인가본데
제 전문이 아닙니다
...this is way out of my league.
기침이 심한데
수의사도 두 손 들었어요
He's got a really bad cough,
and our vet can't stop it.
Is there something you can do?
방법이 없을까요?
Let me see.
가만있자...
봅시다
Do you think you could get him
to eat a bat?
박쥐 한번 먹여 볼래요?